trust.zone 2017-05-17

# Privacy policy. Trust.Zone - The One To Rely On! - Trusted VPN Service

Privacy policy

The rules we hold about your Privacy

We are privacy service and we realize how important it is that our customers fully understand what private information we collect, store and process. Our privacy policy goal is simple: maximizing your privacy.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. This information including only your email address. We using email address to approve your registration and send usefull notifications about our service and your subscription.

All 3rd parties Payments processors can store specific information about payments. You can track their privacy policy for more information during payment process. We are not saving any personal details about the payments in our system.

### What information is logged when customers connect to our VPN service?

All our VPN servers around the world ARE NOT storing any log files to keep your privacy safe. All the usage data is anonymous and not connected to your real, public IP address.

### Data Protection and Encryption

All public and private keys, account and VPN passwords are stored in encrypted format, using strong cryptographic algorithms. Appropriate security measures are taken for the protection of this information against unauthorized access, unauthorized alteration, destruction or disclosure of data.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service remember certain information). We store in cookies only some tech information about your current session after you logged in to our site. No personal information and emails stored in cookies.

### File Sharing Activities, DMCA Notices, illegal activities

You agree that you will not perform any kind of illegal file sharing activities and other illegal activities. Since our customers are anonymous when using our service, such notices are reviewing by our team and will issue an appropriate response. Since we store no connection logs, we couldn't associate a request with a customer identity even if legally compelled to do so.

### Changes to policy

We reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on Feb, 25th 2017.

### Contact us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using Contact page
